{
    "subject": "resource/Roddy_Bottum",
    "predicate": "property/label",
    "object": "resource/Merge_Records",
    "human_readable": "The label of Roddy Bottum is Merge Records.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8962852358818054,
            "question": "With which record label does Roddy Bottum collaborate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8691595196723938,
            "question": "Which record label has signed Roddy Bottum?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.867186427116394,
            "question": "What record label is Roddy Bottum associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8211106657981873,
            "question": "Is Roddy Bottum signed to a specific record label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.744145929813385,
            "question": "What is the name of the record label that houses Roddy Bottum's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7033821940422058,
            "question": "Is Roddy Bottum affiliated with a specific music label?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6790001392364502,
            "question": "To what music label does Roddy Bottum belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5826619267463684,
            "question": "Who represents Roddy Bottum's musical output?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5311537981033325,
            "question": "What is the name of the label that supports Roddy Bottum's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47374385595321655,
            "question": "What company handles the distribution of Roddy Bottum's music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Roddy Bottum is Merge Records.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7768_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the label that supports Roddy Bottum's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7768_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who represents Roddy Bottum's musical output?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7768_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what music label does Roddy Bottum belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7768_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7768_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7768_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7768_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7768_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7768_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7768_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7768_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7768_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7768_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7768_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe triple to be evaluated is \"Roddy Bottum label Merge Records\". \n\nAccording to the documents, in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7768/re-ranker-msmarco/29.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7768/re-ranker-msmarco/36.txt, it is mentioned that Roddy Bottum is associated with Merge Records as a signee of his band Imperial Teen. Therefore, the information supports the triple and hence the output should be \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document mentions that Imperial Teen, the band featuring Roddy Bottum, is signed to Merge Records. Therefore, the statement \"The label of Roddy Bottum is Merge Records\" can be considered correct based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context states Imperial Teen is now signed to Merge Records.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}